《指定幸存者》前情提要
Previously on "Designated Survivor"...
关于北约峰会
It's about the NATO summit.
新任法国大使想谈谈核弹的事
The new French ambassador wanted to talk about nukes.
他们愿意逐步削减军备
It's an opening to De-escalate.
这里的炸药足够炸毁三座国会大厦了
There's enough explosives in here to blow up three Capitols.
她被绑架了
She's been kidnapped.
她在查布朗宁·里德
She was looking into Browning Reed.
威尔士探员认为其前任执行董事
Agent Wells is convinced that
帕特里克·劳埃德涉嫌参与这起阴谋
the ex-C.E.O. Patrick Lloyd's involved with the conspiracy.
我会清除你
I'm brooming any connection between you,
布朗宁·里德以及国会任务之间的联系
Browning Reed, and the Capitol mission.
很快  就不会再有书面记录等等的问题
Soon, there'll be no paper trail whatsoever,
而且威尔士探员已被抓获
and Agent Wells is contained.
埃布·莱纳德已经消化了我给他的一切
Abe Leonard has eaten up everything I've fed him.
那我们什么时候能看到他采取行动
When are we gonna see something from him, then?
应该快了
Any day, I expect.
自从国会袭击案之后
Since the attack at the Capitol,
提及到布朗宁·里德的文件都被删除了
references to Browning Reed have been deleted.
如果我们找到删除文件的人...
If we find out who deleted these files...
我们就找到了叛徒
we find our traitor.
■
注意  所有安保队...
Be advised. All security teams...
指定幸存者
第一季 第二十集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     苏小黛  Michael  酥ki酱  桃子
赛斯  你还好吗
Hey, Seth, you okay?
翻译     murky  长颈鹿  一只虾  子V
我没事  抱歉  我不知道是怎么了
Yeah, I'm sorry. Uh, I-I don't know what's happening.
我通常不会晕机的
I-I don't usually get airsick.
翻译     薇薇安  潇然  星星与野狗
想想的话  这也是你第一次坐空军一号
And to think, it's your first time on Air Force One, too.
赛斯  看着
Hey, Seth, look.
校对     长颈鹿  苏小黛
你可以把这张照片也发给你妈
You can send this one to your mom, as well.
时间轴     壬虚浪影  Avis  姜姜
该打起精神了  孩子
Time to rally, son.
我们着陆前得先应对媒体
We got to gaggle with the press before we land.
后期     虫虫不咬人
总监     MQ小早
公告     人人影视永久官方网站 www.YYeTs.com
请进
Yes.
现在不方便吗
Bad time?
不会  请进
No. Come on in.
我...
I, uh --
我觉得第一次参加国际峰会的压力
I think the pressure of his first international summit
可能把你的新闻发言人吓住了
may have gotten to your press secretary.
不知道你感觉怎么样
And I just wondered how you're doing.
我很好  赛斯没事吧
I'm fine. Is Seth all right?
他没事  只是有点紧张
Yeah, just a case of the jitters.
他会没事的  只要他明白
He'll get over it as soon as he realizes
北约峰会无非就是
that a NATO summit is no different
多语种的超大型内阁会议而已
than an outsized cabinet meeting in a lot of different languages.
希望能有那么简单
I hope it's that simple.
要是我直接提出方案
Are they gonna think that it's presumptuous of me,
他们会觉得我太专横了吗
putting an initiative on the table?
当然不会  你可是美国总统
Hell no. You're the president of the United States.
也对
Right.
我知道我并非像你那般的谈判者
I know I'm not the negotiator that you are --
别看轻自己
Ah, don't sell yourself short.
汤姆  也许我们的处事风格不同
You know, we may have different styles, Tom,
但这恰恰是一个好团队所必须的
but I think that's what makes us a good team.
有学者也有政客
The professor and the politician.
你负责提供事实  我负责强迫他们接受
You give them the facts, and I'll twist their arms.
我觉得行
That works for me.
我知道这对你来说有多重要
I know how important this is to you.
是啊
Yeah.
如果当初我连任  军备控制本会是我的首要目标
The arms control was going to be a priority of my second term.
现在这是我们的首要目标
Well... now it's our priority.
我不关心你们加了多少班
I don't care about your overtime.
不  你们得找遍每个角落
No, you search everywhere...
要是都找过了  就再找一遍
and then when you've done that, search it again.
还是没发现吗
Still nothing?
没有  我让国内的所有机构都去找了
No. I got every agency in the country looking.
她知道怎么照顾自己
She knows how to take care of herself.
是的
Yeah.
布朗宁·里德查得怎么样了
Where are you with the Browning Reed investigation?
我让恰克·拉辛克来帮忙了
I got Chuck Russink coming in to help out.
拉辛克  不是吧  他可不靠谱
Russink? You serious? He's a space cadet.
汉娜相信他
Hannah trusts him.
看来真是不顾一切了
Whatever it takes, I guess.
我准备买单的  罗迪斯女士
I was gonna pay, Ms. Rhodes.
真的不用  我来就行
No, seriously. I'll get it.
服务员呢
Where's our server?
失陪一下
Will you guys excuse me a second?
好的
Yeah.
你好
Hey, you.
你好  很高兴见到你
How you doing? It's good to see you.
艾米丽·罗迪斯
Emily Rhodes,
这是我表妹纳迪娅·埃斯皮诺萨
meet my cousin, Nadia Espinosa.
很高兴见到你
It's a pleasure.
你老板是吉田议员  对吧
You work for Congresswoman Yoshida, right?
没错
That's right.
-怎么样  -我很喜欢这工作
- How's that going? - I love it.
我很高兴能跟优秀的人一起合作
I mean, it's great to be able to collaborate with good people.
你们俩真的是亲戚吗
Are you sure you two are related?
是的  我也觉得奇怪
Yeah, I wonder all the time.
我想再来一杯啤酒  你们需要什么吗
I need another beer. Do you guys want anything?
-不用了  谢谢  -不用了  谢谢
- No, I'm good, thanks. - No, thank you.
听说总统去多伦多了
So, POTUS is heading up to Toronto.
是的  白宫归我管了
Yes. The White House is all mine.
说正经的  这是他第一次参加北约峰会
No, seriously, it's his first NATO summit.
第一次作为总统出国
First time out of the country.
民调支持率很高
Polls are high.
他势如破竹  你也是
I mean, he's on a roll. So are you.
我不得不承认  这感觉很爽
I do have to admit, it feels good.
你呢  你会继续跟着霍斯拉滕吗
What about you? Are you gonna follow Hookstraten?
不  她是邀请我了  不过
No, she did offer, but...
我觉得我不适合为教育部长工作
I don't see myself working for the Secretary of Education.
这工作可不刺激
It's not exactly the fast lane.
这么说吧  在白宫工作过后
Let's just say, after you work in the West Wing,
其他任何工作都感觉是被贬了
everything feels like a step down.
你可要知道
Well, just so you know,
我并没有反对让霍斯拉滕当副总统
I was not opposed to Hookstraten for V.P.
我觉得要是能继续合作就更好了
I think it would've been great to be working together again.
是的  一定的
Yeah, it would've been.
这是华盛顿  什么都有可能发生  对吧
It's Washington. Anything can happen, right?
通常是的
And it usually does.
是的
Yeah.
我该回去了
I should get back.
谢谢过来打招呼
Thanks for stopping by.
我们会参加一个半小时的接待会
So, we attend the general reception for 30 minutes,
照照相什么的
smile for the cameras,
然后我们就回迎宾套房
then we retreat to a hospitality suite
那是我为与北约核计划小组几个
I set up for select members
特定成员国的领导人会面而准备的
of the Nuclear Planning Group.
这样我们就能在全体大会前
That gives us a chance to start some lobbying
-进行游说了  -这招厉害
- before the general session. - Smart.
我可是老手了  年轻人
Well, it's not my first rodeo, son.
我们的首要目标
Now, our primary target
是法国总理贾丝廷·马塞特
is French Prime Minister Justine Massett.
雷厉风行  且如圣女贞德般爱国
Sharp as a tack and as chauvinistic as Joan of Arc.
法国传奇女英雄
她可能会很难对付
She can be very prickly.
为什么呢  一开始可是法国想要
Why would she be? It was the French who wanted us
让我们提出裁减军备的
to bring up arms reduction in the first place.
但那是私下说的
Yes. Privately.
但在北约其他国家面前
But in front of NATO,
法国想让我们先提出这个议案
the French want us to bring up the initiative first,
好让他们有个机会先批评一下
giving them an opportunity to criticize
如果他们想的话  甚至可以食言
or even withdraw, if they so choose.
这都是套路
It's all part of the game --
没到必要的时候别当出头鸟
don't stick your neck out if you don't have to.
下一个是乔纳斯·格洛特克
Then there's Jonas Grottke,
刚刚连任德国总理
just re-elected as German Chancellor.
同时他也是北约核计划小组的主席
He's also a chairman of NATO's Nuclear Planning Group.
强大的盟友  他能为你说话
Strong ally. Got you covered there.
很好  需要担心的事情又少了点
Good. One less thing for me to worry about.
而我不了解的人是阿鲁娜·马哈詹
The one unknown to me is Aruna Mahajan.
英国史上第一位印度裔首相
The first British Indian prime minister in U.K. history.
极端的无党派者  但能在极其动荡的情况下
Fiercely independent but was able to forge a coalition
建立起政治联盟
and under extremely turbulent conditions.
我们有一些共同点
Well, we have something in common.
确实
True enough.
我可以的
I can work with that.
什么
What?
谢谢
Thank you.
求救  求救  我是联调局探员
Mayday, mayday. This is FBI Agent
汉娜·威尔士  求救
Hannah Wells. Mayday.
联调局探员汉娜·威尔士  求救
FBI Agent Hannah Wells. Mayday.
求救  我是...汉娜·威尔士
Mayday. This is... Hannah Wells.
汉娜·威尔士  这里是印第安河流域
Hannah Wells, this is Coast Guard Station 142,
海岸警卫队142号站
Indian River.
海岸警卫队142号站呼叫汉娜·威尔士船只
Coast Guard Station 142 calling the ship Hannah Wells.
我是联调局探员汉娜·威尔士
This is FBI Agent Hannah Wells.
求...
Mayda...
首先  我要感谢各位的出席
To begin, I want to thank you all for being here.
正如你们知道的  明天除了常规安排以外
As you know, in addition to tomorrow's regular schedule,
美国将会提出一个缩减
the United States will be introducing an initiative
北约成员国核武库的提案
that would reduce NATO's nuclear arsenal.
我想要明确一点
Now, I want to be absolutely clear
这是一项削减军备的提案
that this is a proposed weapons-reduction change,
并非正式声明
not a change in doctrine.
而且这完全建立在俄罗斯联邦
And it's entirely predicated upon the Russian Federation
响应北约号召
scaling back its strategic nuclear weapons
而按比缩减战略性核武器的基础上
in proportional response to NATO's actions,
俄罗斯总统已向我保证
something that the Russian president
他已经准备好实施了
has assured me he is ready to do.
你相信他吗  科内留斯
What, you believe him, Cornelius?
嗯  我相信
Yeah, I do.
基于什么
On what basis?
基于我们二十年的情谊
On the basis of our 20-year relationship
我能准确分辨出他是否在撒谎
and being able to tell when he's lying and when he's not.
而且还建立在能使我们的家园变得
And based on the fact that it is in the interest of all sides
更稳定  更安全的举措
to agree on anything
是完全符合各国利益的事实基础之上的
that will lead to a more stable and secure planet.
尽管最近世界秩序遭到破坏
Despite recent disruptions to the world order,
但现在不是回去搞孤立主义或民粹主义的时候
this is not the time to retreat into isolationism or populism.
现在是展现全球合作可以也将会
This is the time to show that global cooperation
指引我们创造更安全的未来的时候
can and will lead us to a safer future.
更何况我们用以保管核武器的设备方法
Not to mention that the way that we keep our nuclear arsenals
耗资巨大
is insanely expensive.
真有趣  总统先生
It's intriguing, Mr. President,
但波兰和斯洛伐克没有核武器
but Poland and Slovakia have no nuclear weapons of our own.
我们依赖美国提供的"核保护伞"
We rely on your American nuclear umbrellas.
所以你要如何保证削减核军备后
So what can you offer by way of a guarantee
我们的和平与安全依然能受到保护呢
that our peace and our safety will still be protected?
现在我能给的只是承诺
The closest thing I can offer to a guarantee is my word,
不是以汤姆·柯克曼
not as Tom Kirkman,
而是以美国总统的身份作出的承诺
but as President of the United States,
你最坚定的盟友
your most steadfast ally.
你可以相信他  约瑟夫
You can believe him there, Jozef.
我们都能相信他
We can all believe him.
很显然  我希望明天峰会能获得你们的支持
Obviously, I am hoping for your support at tomorrow's summit.
谢谢
Thank you.
法方很期待你的提案
France looks forward to your proposal.
感激不尽  女士
I appreciate that, Madame.
这不是白宫之旅
This isn't on the White House tour.
进出威尔士探员办公室的通道是受到严格保密的
Access to Agent Wells' office is extremely restricted.
汉娜在哪
Where is Hannah?
出外勤了
On assignment.
能恢复那些被删的关于布朗宁·里德的文件吗
Any chance we can recover those deleted Browning Reed files?
你是说不用时光机吗
Not without a time machine.
有人运行了一个强制删除程序
Someone ran a brute-force deletion program.
那是数据清除工具的始祖
It's the mother of data erasers.
已经把数据从白宫服务器上彻底删除了
Cleaned them right off the White House servers.
那我们什么都查不到了
So we got nothing.
我可没这么说
I didn't say that.
因为一开始有大批文件需要处理
Because there were so many files to begin with,
不管是谁在湮灭证据
whoever's been covering their tracks
他在过去几个月里分多次少量删除了这批文件
has been deleting them in small batches over the past few months.
与布朗宁·里德有关的文件
There are only five files
现在只剩下五份
still remaining associated with Browning Reed.
你需要把它们拷贝并打印出来
Gonna need you to make copies and print them up.
看一下这个
Check this out.
这是删除档案的那个人
It's a digital fingerprint left behind
留下的数位指纹
by the person who deleted the files.
数位指纹是独一无二的  如果我够厉害
Now, they tend to be unique, but if I'm good --
我觉得自己的确挺厉害的
and I like to think I am --
我可以在这些文件里植入追踪程序
I can program a trace and plant it in the remaining files.
如果叛徒试图删除其中任何一份文件
So if the traitor tries to delete any of them,
我们就能追踪到对方的IP地址
we can track the user back to an exact I.P. address.
正是如此
Exactly.
你需要多长时间编写追踪程序
How long will it take you to build a trace?
-几个小时吧  -给你一小时
- A few hours? - You got one.
那些文件是查出内鬼的唯一线索
Those files are the only lead to the insider,
一旦被删除  就什么都不剩了
and once they're deleted, we got nothing.
真是"毫无压力"啊
No pressure, huh?
谢谢  好的  非常感谢
Well, thank you. Yes. Thank you very much.
搞定了
Well, that's it.
我们的提案被确定为第三项议程
Our proposal is the third item on the agenda.
胜利在望了
We're on our way.
-现场没有媒体吧  -没有
- No media, right? - Nope.
只有你和其他27位国家领导人
Just you and 27 other leaders of the free world.
放松点  汤姆
Relax, Tom.
我们想要的只是开启一个早就该进行的会谈
All we're asking is to start a conversation that's long overdue.
请进
Come in.
赛斯
Seth.
抱歉打扰您  总统先生
Hey. Sorry to disturb you, Mr. President.
我只是觉得您应该马上看看这个
I just, um, thought you should see this right away.
艾尔萨卡并非国会爆炸案的真凶
-为什么事先没人提醒我们  -有啊
- Why didn't we get a heads-up? - We did.
几天前埃布问过我艾尔萨卡的事  记得吗
Abe asked me about Al-Sakar a couple days ago, remember?
是的
Right.
我们搪塞过去了  我以为这事已经了结了
We stonewalled. I thought that was the end of it.
但他还是发表了文章
Then he published anyway.
我们接下来怎么办
So, what's our plan?
这简直是胡说八道
This is total crap!
我们马上商量解决办法
We're figuring that out right now.
我回头再打给你
I'll call you back.
我认识埃布·莱纳德  他曾是位优秀的记者
I knew Abe Leonard. He was a good reporter
直到他开始利用消息来源肆意妄为
until he started getting fast and loose with his sources.
把这个新闻压下来对你来说应该不在话下
You should have no problem shooting this one down.
告诉他们这只是一派胡言
Just tell them it's nothing but a big pack of lies.
不  我希望我们承认这是一种猜想
No, I want our position to be that this is conjecture,
但我们会对所有的指控展开调查
but we will investigate all of the allegations.
抱歉  总统先生
Sorry, sir.
如果这并非事实为何不直接公开否认呢
Why not just openly deny it if it's not true?
赛斯说得对
Seth's right.
此刻回避只会招来更多质疑声
Deflecting this now is only gonna raise suspicion.
是的  美国公民相信我们抓获的恐怖分子
Yeah, the American people believe that we captured
就是国会爆炸案的真凶
the terrorists responsible for the Capitol bombing.
这篇报道扬言我们抓错了人
This article says that we got the wrong guy.
我是说  如果我们现在不用力反击
I mean, if we don't push back hard now,
民众会对政府丧失信心的
confidence in the administration's gonna tank.
你可以说政府相信
You can say that we're standing by
我们的情报机构和军方官员
our intelligence agencies and our military officials.
抱歉  总统先生
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
我想这么做远远不够
I don't think that goes far enough.
就这么写  然后拿给我看
Just write it up and bring it back to me!
好的  总统先生
Yes, sir.
那是怎么一回事
What the hell was that?
这就是我的处理方式
It's how I have to handle this.
要知道这篇报道极大的损害了你的公信力
You realize this story puts your credibility at risk.
如果现在不粉碎谣言的话  你的就任百天计划
Your 100 days, everything we want to do here,
我们现在做的一切  全都会付之东流
goes right out the window if you don't crush this right now.
-我无法这么做  -为什么
- I can't. - Why not?
因为这是真的
Because it's true.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
本土阴谋
A homegrown conspiracy?
白宫内的潜在叛徒
A possible traitor in the White House?
是的
Yeah.
你都没告诉我
And you didn't tell me?
事关国家安全
It was a matter of security.
艾米丽和赛斯都不知道
Emily doesn't know. Neither does Seth.
我可是你的国务卿啊
Well, I'm your Secretary of State, for God's sake.
我可是在总统继承顺位上啊
I mean, I-I'm in the line of succession.
你觉得你无法信任我吗
You didn't think you could trust me?
-这和信任无关  -胡说八道
- This isn't a matter of trust. - The hell it's not!
为了你我重新出山
Now, I came out of retirement for you.
我把我的一世英名交到你的手上
I put my legacy on the line for you!
你就是这样报答我的
And this is how you repay me?!
-我以为我控制住局面了  -你错了
- I thought I had it handled. - Well, you were wrong.
你大错特错
You were dead wrong,
现在我和你成了一根线上的蚂蚱
and now my head is on the block right along with yours!
我应该早点让你知道的
Well, I probably should've let you in.
这真是年度最不负责任的陈述啊
That is the understatement of the year.
我见过你之前的判断失误
I have seen you exercise poor judgment before,
但都无法和这次相比  汤姆
Tom, but this takes the cake!
科内留斯  如果我冒犯你了我很抱歉
Cornelius, I'm sorry if I offended you.
我也不想这样
It's the last thing I wanted to do.
但是美国总统有义务
But the president of the United States has a responsibility
保护机密信息和正在进行的调查
to protect classified information and ongoing investigations.
这根本不是意图误导美国民众
This isn't a matter of trying to mislead the American people.
这是为了保护他们
This is about trying to protect them.
你应该了解这点
And you should know that.
我犯了错  我很抱歉
Now, I've made a mistake, and I am sorry.
但现在我需要你的指导
But right now I need your counsel.
我有哪些选择
What are my options?
问题是你没有任何选择
You don't have any. That's the problem.
不作伪证的话无法否认这篇报道
You can't deny the story without committing perjury,
不承认你仍不知道真凶身份的话
and you can't confirm it without admitting
你就无法证实这篇报道
that you still don't know who's behind all this,
这会让整个美国陷入恐慌
throwing the whole American country into a panic.
所以我们需要赛斯帮我们争取些时间
That's why we need Seth to buy us some time.
需要多久
But how much time?
总统先生  我们已经身处狼穴了
The jackals are at the door, Mr. President.
我觉得我们快知道真相了
I think we're really close to cracking this thing.
真的吗
Do you really?
你的首席探员失踪了  可能已经死了
Your lead investigator is missing, possibly dead.
试图杀你的人依旧活着
The man who tried to kill you is still alive.
白宫里的叛徒身份依然成谜
And the mole in the White House remains unknown.
在我看来你就好像全押在了
It looks to me like you're doubling down
一手特别烂的牌上
on a mighty poor hand.
但我别无选择了
Well, it's the only hand I was given.
好吧
All right.
我们只有厚着脸皮上了
We brass it out.
我是摩斯
This is Moss.
好
Yes.
当然  我们马上就到
Of course. We'll be right there.
我们的盟友希望我们到楼下去
Our allies have requested our presence downstairs.
他们希望我们能解释一下那篇报道
They want an explanation for the story.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
我们邀请到
We're joined now
今天《纽约标准》报道的作者
by Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Abe Leonard,
普利策奖得主埃布·莱纳德
whose story in today's New York Standard
该报道挑起了一系列严峻的问题
has raised serious questions
艾尔萨卡并非国会爆炸案的真凶
到底谁才是国会爆炸案的真凶
about who was really responsible for the attack on our Capitol.
-欢迎你  埃布  -谢谢  很高兴来到这里
- Welcome, Abe. - Thank you. It's good to be here.
我们由头条标题说起吧
Let's start with the big headline.
艾尔萨卡没有炸毁国会大厦吗
Al-Sakar did not blow up the Capitol?
没有  他们没有相应的人力财力
No. They didn't have the money or the manpower.
他们的头目马吉德·纳萨尔是为了钱出来背锅的
Their leader, Majid Nassar, was paid to take credit.
谁给的钱
Paid? By whom?
内斯特·洛萨诺
Nestor Lozano,
试图行刺柯克曼总统的人
the man who tried to assassinate President Kirkman.
但政府却将目标锁定在马吉德·纳萨尔身上
Yet our government went after Majid Nassar --
他们在一次海豹突击行动中将纳萨尔抓获
actually captured him in a S.E.A.L. team raid
突击队指挥官也在那次行动中殉职
where the commanding officer was killed.
我认为他们被误导了
I believe they were misled.
被谁误导了
Misled by whom?
差劲的情报机关
Bad intelligence.
他们相信了洛萨诺设的套
They bought the story Lozano was selling.
那洛萨诺到底在保护谁呢
But who was he protecting?
静音
我是惠特克
Whitaker.
你有看埃布·莱纳德在电视上的讲话吗
Are you watching Abe Leonard on television?
没  但我看了他的报道
No, but I read his story.
奏效了
It's all working.
所有人的注意力都在联调局那边  而非我们
Everyone's focused on the FBI, not us.
很好  但他从哪里获得了洛萨诺的消息
Well, that's great, but where did he get this stuff about Lozano?
我不知道  是他自己做的调查
I don't know. He did that on his own.
那么他踩入了雷区
Well, he's treading on dangerous ground.
不算吧  他认为洛萨诺死了
Not really. He thinks Lozano's dead,
和其他人一样
just like everyone else.
艾尔萨卡并非国会爆炸案的真凶
埃布·莱纳德已经没有利用价值了
Abe Leonard has served his purpose.
知道了
Roger that.
正如我所说  总统非常相信
As I said, the president stands
我们的情报机关以及军方机构
by our intelligence community and our military.
回答问题  赛斯
Answer the question, Seth.
艾尔萨卡炸毁了国会大厦吗
Did Al-Sakar blow up the Capitol?
根据当前的官方说法  是艾尔萨卡没错
That is the official explanation at this time.
有改变的可能性是吗
But it could change?
我只想说  我们正深入展开调查
All I said is we're looking into the allegations.
这意味着  你并不清楚吗
So does that mean you don't know?
是意味着调查正在进行中
It means we're looking into it.
-赛斯  -请提问
- Seth! - Yes.
柯克曼总统在北约峰会上讲的是
El presidente Kirkman está  diciendo la verdad
真话吗
a la cumbre De la OTAN?
听到了吗  终于有关于北约的问题了
Ah, see? A question about NATO.
很遗憾  我的西班牙语不是很好
Unfortunately, my Spanish is no longer as good.
你能重复一遍问题吗
Could you repeat the question?
请谅解
Perdon.
柯克曼总统在北约峰会上讲的是实话吗
Is President Kirkman telling the NATO summit the truth?
我已经回答过这个问题了
I've already answered this question.
当然是实话啊
Of course he's telling the truth.
《纽约标准》
如果总统相信他的情报机构
If the president stands by his intelligence,
为什么还要对该指控展开调查呢
why is he looking into the allegations?
我一直在明确这点
Sure. So, I've tried to be perfectly clear.
你想要答案  总统也是
You want answers. The president wants answers.
所以他才展开调查  知道吗
Which is why he is looking into the allegations, okay?
稍后他会寻找一个恰当的时间
And he'll make a statement to the public
发表公开讲话
at the appropriate time,
白宫针对国会爆炸案模棱两可的回应
但如今他正专注于他的首次北约峰会之行
but right now he is focused on the first NATO summit,
所以我想大家提一些关于这方面的问题
which is what I would love to answer questions about.
我是法索
This is Foerstel.
特别探员法索
Special Agent Foerstel,
我是军士长露西·费尔南德兹
this is Chief Petty Officer Lucy Fernandez,
隶属海岸警卫队  负责特拉华州印第安河流域
U.S. Coast Guard, Indian River, Delaware.
我们昨晚收到了汉娜·威尔士的求救信号
We received a mayday call from Hannah Wells last night.
-你们找到她了吗  -还没有  先生
- You found her? - Not exactly, sir.
由于求救信号受到了静电干扰
Uh, because of the static of the distress call,
我们起初以为汉娜·威尔士是一艘船
we thought that Hannah Wells was a ship.
使用数字滤波器对信号进行处理后
It wasn't until we ran the call through a digital filter
我们才意识到她说的是"联调局探员威尔士"
that we realized she was saying "FBI Agent Hannah Wells."
我没明白
Okay. I don't understand.
-你到底找到她没有  -没有
- Do you have her or not? - We don't.
为了回应求救信号
In response to the mayday,
我们紧急出动了一艘H-65救援直升机及救生船
we scrambled an H-65 helicopter and a response boat
前往信号发射地
to the coordinates,
但一无所获
but the results were negative.
好吧  所以现在是什么情况
Okay. So where does this leave us?
我们正扩大搜索网格区域
Uh, we're working on a broadened search grid,
将可变因素考虑进去  但这需要时间
factoring in current changes, but it's gonna take time.
好吧  我一小时内过去
All right. I'm gonna be there within the hour.
希望你们到时候能给出更好的回答
I'm gonna want better answers than that.
彼得·麦克利什与我情同手足
Peter MacLeish was a brother to me.
你杀了我的亲人
You kill my family...
我也杀你的
I kill yours.
杰森
Jason...
早上好
Good morning.
我知道由于今晨《纽约标准》发表的文章
I know that there has been a great deal of speculation
外界流言四起
with regards to an article
大家均有诸多猜测
that was published in this morning's New York Standard.
虽然我无法证实或反驳该说法
Although I cannot confirm or deny the allegations,
但我可以很自信地告诉各位
I can tell you in confidence
美国政府正在进行深入调查
that my government is in the middle of an extensive investigation
而调查需要高度保密
that is highly classified.
很遗憾  此时此刻
Unfortunately at this time,
由于涉及到国家安全
I cannot share that information with you
我无法向大家透露更多信息
because of reasons of national security.
总统先生  我们一定会继续支持你
Mr. President, you can be assured of our continued support.
谢谢你  总理
Thank you, Chancellor.
本着互相理解的精神
Then, in the spirit of mutual understanding,
我建议我们回到
I suggest that we move over
裁剪核军备的提案上
to the initiative regarding nuclear disarmament.
抱歉  总统先生
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
但法方不同意
But France is not satisfied.
我想提醒一下新任的美国总统
May I remind the new American president
当你下令要在阿尔及利亚
that when he initiated a mission
抓捕马吉德·纳萨尔时
to capture Majid Nassar in Algeria,
我们给予了美军使用法国领空的许可
we allowed him to use French airspace.
你们还利用了西班牙的雷达装备
Spanish radar assets and Italian naval support
以及意大利的海军资源
were also employed.
而现在我们必须要面对的事实是
Now, we must all face the fact that we supported you
美方可能有意欺骗我们提供军事支持
under what might turn into c.
我们有权知道
We deserve to know
艾尔萨卡是否真的并非国会爆炸案的真凶
if Al-Sakar did not perpetrate the Capitol bombing.
恐怕我国政府也持相同意见  总统先生
I'm afraid my government agrees, Mr. President.
我们已经从伊拉克吸取到了教训
We have learned from our mistakes in Iraq.
在未得知事情真相前
We cannot discuss your initiative any further
我们无法进一步讨论您的提案
without knowing the truth.
请容我说几句
If my esteemed colleagues will excuse me,
各位不会真觉得
you are not seriously suggesting
法国及英国手上没有因涉及国家安全
that the French and British don't have classified intelligence
而必须进行保密的情报吧
that they keep secret for reasons of national security.
当然
Mais oui.
我们当然也有  摩斯国务卿
Of course we have our discretions, Secretary Moss.
但我们也有理由互相信任
But we also have reason to trust each other,
毕竟我们有长期合作的经验
a long history of cooperation and experience.
而我们和柯克曼先生没有共事过
Monsieur Kirkman has no such history.
他能当上总统
He is president only because
只是因为前政府被消灭了
the previous government was wiped out.
不  我的意思是
No, my point is...
我们要如何去相信一个...
how can we trust someone who appears to be a --
哪个词来着
What's the word?
愚蠢的  笨拙的
Gaffeur. Maladroit.
我想你是想说"糊涂虫"
I believe the word you're searching for is "Blunderer."
是的
Oui.
你让我们协助你去追捕一个错误的目标
Who apparently abused article five of the NATO charter
这显然违反了《北约宪章》第五条
by asking us to assist him in going after the wrong target.
正如我之前所说  夫人
As I said earlier, Madame,
我不方便对我已发表的言论
I am not at liberty to comment on that any further
做出深入的评价
than I already have.
那法国方面建议
Then France proposes tabling any discussion
搁置对美方提案的一切讨论
of the U.S. Initiative
直到总统先生能给出更多的表态
until the president can say more and does.
我能做的...
All I can do...
只有请求大家
is ask you all, please...
请不要让我国国内的问题
please do not allow my nation's domestic issues
影响到我们的全球目标
to interfere with our global objectives.
我提请核计划集团
Then I move to have the Nuclear Planning Group
今日午后再次讨论这项提案
revisit the initiative this afternoon.
核计划集团
The Nuclear Planning Group
将在上午的会议后  重新考虑
will meet after the morning session to...reconsider.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在我们来讨论一些日程上
Now let's move to some of the less...
争议没那么大的项目吧
controversial items on our agenda.
追踪器已经安装好了
The trace has been planted.
如果有人想删这些电子文件
If someone deletes these digital files,
我们就能追踪到那混蛋了
we'll be able to track the bastard.
别留到后面一起感谢我啊
Don't thank me all at once.
好了  好了
All right, all right. Way to go, Abe!
谢谢  非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
谢谢  回去工作吧  够了
Thank you. Go back to work. Enough.
好了  谢谢各位
All right, thank you.
好了  感谢各位
All right. Thank you very much.
-太棒了  做得好  -谢谢
- Good job. Great job. - Thank you.
你没收到我的短信吗
You didn't get my texts?
我在忙着让我们成名
Well, I've been busy making us famous.
进来
Come in.
埃布·莱纳德  这是艾丽莎·阿布德
Abe Leonard, Alyssa Abboud.
我们是要讨论晋升机会吗
Uh, are we here to discuss promotional opportunities?
事实上  艾丽莎是来提供法律意见的
Actually, Alyssa's from Legal.
联调局想跟你谈话
The FBI wants to talk to you.
真是意料之中啊
That's so predictable.
只是没想到这么快
I just didn't expect it this soon.
埃布
Abe --
好几周了  他们都不肯听我的电话
For weeks, I couldn't get them on the phone.
他们甚至派人跟踪我想吓跑我
They even put a tail on me to try and scare me off.
怎么  现在他们倒想跟我谈话了
What? Now they want to talk?
得了吧  我不会跟他们谈的
I mean, forget it. I'm not talking to them.
我们希望你去谈
We'd like you to.
抱歉  你说什么
I'm sorry. What?
他们认为你可能是国会爆炸案调查中的
They believe that you could be a potential witness
潜在目击者
in their investigation into the Capitol bombing.
不可能  我不会供出我的消息来源的
No way. I'm not giving up my sources!
没有人要你这么做
No one's asking you to.
那你们要我做什么
So what are you asking me?
就参加一个简单的问询  仅此而已
To go in for an interview. That's all.
-看看他们想要什么  -凭什么
- See what they want. - Why should I?
因为如果你拒绝  他们可以传唤你
Because they can subpoena you if you don't.
行啊  让他们尽管来
Fine. Let 'em.
艾丽莎的意思是  如果你自愿去
What Alyssa's saying is if you go in voluntarily,
对你和杂志社都有好处
it buys good will, for you and the paper --
毕竟社里给你提供了时间  金钱和支持
the paper that gave you the time and money
让你拿到了这个报道
and support to get this story.
也许还能因他们的麻烦再赢个普利策奖呢
Yeah, and possibly pick up another Pulitzer for their troubles.
我请求你  埃布
I'm asking you, Abe.
社里希望你去
This is what New York wants.
这对我很重要
It's important to me.
好吧
Okay.
那就这么定了吧
Well, I guess it's a date.
我们一小时后从这里出发
We'll leave together from here. One hour.
她有什么不满啊
What's her problem?
她代表新闻记者方出席
She represents journalists.
你还没跟我说空军一号的事呢
You never told me about Air Force One.
真不敢相信你居然选在今天问我这种事
I can't believe you're asking me about that on a day like this.
我想知道情况怎么样啊
I want to know how it went.
我现在都要忙疯了  艾米丽
I'm really crazy-busy right now, Emily.
每个人现在都忙疯了  赛斯
Everyone is crazy-busy right now, Seth.
你就快点告诉我吧
Really quickly, just tell me,
一切都如你所愿吗
was it everything you'd hoped it'd be?
这么说吧  我的预期
Let's just say that the anticipation
被现实打败了
far outweighed the actual event.
我也是这么听说的
So I heard.
你什么意思  摩斯告诉你了
What do you mean? Moss told you?
他好像给我发了张照片
He may have sent me a photo.
我们友尽了
We are no longer friends.
美国海岸警卫队
费尔南德兹  我是法索探员
Fernandez? Agent Foerstel.
-很高兴见到你  -请汇报最新情况
- Nice to meet you. - Status update.
我们的搜索面积覆盖了这一整片区域
We've covered this entire area.
目前没有消息
So far, nothing.
这不能接受
It's unacceptable.
那艘船肯定关掉了应答器
The ship must have disabled its transponder.
再加上海浪汹涌及飞机的飞行下限
You add in rough seas and a low ceiling,
更使我们的搜索难度加倍了
it makes the search twice as difficult.
我需要你动用手头的一切资源
I need you to put every resource you have on this.
已经在做了  先生
It's already being done, sir.
但以我的经验来看
But, in my experience,
要找到一艘不愿被发现的船是很难的
it's hard to find a ship that doesn't want to be found.
我不管  找到它
I don't care. Find it.
请进
Come in.
这是我们为下午的会议起草的文稿
It's the readout we drafted for the afternoon session --
除去了美方提案的部分
minus the U.S. Initiative.
只是些标准套路
It's just standard boilerplate.
如果您没意见的话  我就发给记者团
If you're good with it, I'll get it out to the pool.
没问题  发吧
This is fine. Send it out.
-谢谢  -赛斯
- Thank you. - Seth...
感谢你今天下午所做的一切
Thank you for what you did this afternoon.
您是说在世界舞台上垂死挣扎吗
You mean dying on the world stage?
是啊
Yeah.
糟透了对吧
Pretty awful, wasn't it?
我就直说了
Well, look, I'll be honest.
那只是我做的又一个绘声绘色的简报
It was one of my more colorful briefings.
但您的工作比我的要艰巨多了  尤其是现在
But your job is way harder than mine, especially right now.
感谢你能这么说
I appreciate you saying that.
我也很感激你没有要求更多消息
And I appreciate you not asking for more information.
我认识您有一段时间了  总统先生
Well, I've known you for a while now, sir.
足以让我知道  当您做出一个决定时
Long enough to know that, uh, when you make a decision,
一定是有充分理由的  这对我来说就够了
it's for a good reason, and that's good enough for me.
只是希望媒体也能够满意
Just wish it was good enough for the press.
是啊
Yeah.
抱歉  这可能是重要消息
Excuse me. This might be important.
赛斯·怀特
Seth Wright.
谢谢
Thank you.
核计划小组表决了
The Nuclear Planning Group voted.
他们不会将您的提案重新提上议程
They're not gonna be putting your initiative back on the agenda.
那也没办法了
So that's it then.
总统先生  第一夫人打电话找您
Sir, the First Lady's on the phone for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我很遗憾  总统先生
I'm sorry, sir.
下次再来
Next time.
艾丽克斯
Alex.
一切都还好吧
Everything all right?
我们没事  你呢
We're fine. How are you?
我不太好
I've been better.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我知道这一定很不容易
I know this can't be easy.
是啊
No.
我整天都在想你
So, I've -- I've been thinking about you all day.
你知道的  那个新闻
You know, the story.
我觉得我理解了
I-I think I understand.
理解什么
Understand what?
你在医院里不肯告诉我发生了什么
You shutting me out at the hospital
当那个联邦调查局探员去见你的时候
when that FBI agent came to see you...
每次麦克走进来时你的反应
the way you react every time Mike enters a room...
还有你不让我们的家庭
the reason you can't let the family
回白宫住的原因
come back to the White House.
那是真的  是吧
It's true, isn't it?
炸毁国会大厦的另有其人
Someone else blew up the Capitol,
但你并不知道是谁  对吗
and you don't know who it is, do you?
汤姆
Tom?
有太多事情我一直都想告诉你
There are so many things I've wanted to tell you.
现在仍想告诉你
So many things I still want to tell you.
但是你不能
But you can't.
我在想
I was thinking,
一年前
a year ago...
我在工作日唯一需要担心的
the only thing I ever had to worry about on a weekday
就是我能否按时去看佩妮的足球训练
was whether or not I'd get to Penny's soccer practice on time.
这像是上辈子的事了
That is a lifetime ago.
是啊
Yeah.
汤姆  我能怎么帮你
Tom, how can I help you?
别对我失去信心
Don't lose faith in me.
拜托
Come on.
我是永远支持你的  不是吗
I'm always on your side, right?
好吗  知道了  谢谢
Okay? Got it. Thanks.
我们应该找到他们了
I think we found 'em.
在哪儿
Where?
巴尔的摩港口
Port of Baltimore.
他们刚刚接到了一艘未经安排出航的货轮
They just received a call from an unscheduled freighter
发出的呼叫  要求卸货  位置已锁定
looking to unload cargo. Location works out.
大概什么时候抵达
When it's estimated to arrive?
不到一小时  216号船位
Less than an hour. Slip 216.
我是法索
Yes. Foerstel.
我需要一个人质拯救小组
I need an HRT en route to
去巴尔的摩港口216号船位
the Port of Baltimore, Slip 216.
我会去那儿和他们汇合
I'm gonna meet them there.
莱纳德先生  谢谢你过来
Mr. Leonard, thank you for coming in.
这是我的荣幸
My pleasure.
我们可以开始了吗
Should we get started?
我必须回答这个问题吗
Do I have to answer that?
你不同意
You don't agree.
我可没这么说
That's not what I'm saying.
但你觉得这成不了
But you don't think it'll work.
我的想法现在并不重要
What I think doesn't matter right now.
这是总统的想法
It's what the president thinks.
而我支持总统
And I support the president.
马塞特首相
Now, Prime Minister Massett
同意给你五分钟时间
has agreed to give you five minutes.
所以
So...
好好利用起来
Make 'em count.
五分钟后见
See you in five minutes.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你来见我  夫人
Thank you, Madame, for seeing me.
你理解我们为什么将提案移出了议程吧
You understand why we took the initiative off of the agenda.
我不赞成  但是是的  我理解
I did not agree with it, but, yes, I understand.
我需要赢得你的信任
I need to earn your trust.
不只是我  还有所有北约成员国
Oh, not just me. All of NATO.
好吧
Fine.
但我想从法方开始
But I would like to start with France.
这个削减武器之梦是我们一起开启的
We began this dream of weapons reduction together.
我也需要你来完成这个梦
And I will need you there to finish it.
你打算怎么做呢
And how do you expect to do that?
我会向你证明美方
By proving to you that the United States is serious
在削减核威胁上是认真的
about reducing the nuclear threat.
我国拥有200枚导弹
My country has 200 missiles
散布在欧洲各地的地堡中
in bunkers scattered across Europe.
俄罗斯的数量是我们的两倍
Russia has twice that number.
老式的确保相互摧毁
The old dogmas of mutually assured destruction
对阵二次打击能力的教条
versus secondary strike capabilities
需要严肃地重新审核
need to be seriously re-examined,
尤其考虑到我们的控制系统
especially given the threat
有被黑入的风险
of our control systems being hacked.
这可是个骇人的想法
It's a terrifying thought.
没错
Yes, it is.
外面部署的武器越多
And the more weapons that are out there,
出现闪失的可能性就越大
the greater chance something could go wrong.
对我来说很简单
For me, it is very simple.
我们想给后代留下怎样的世界
What kind of a world do we want to leave our children?
你是个梦想家  总统先生
You are a dreamer, sir.
没错
Yes.
没错  我是
Yes, I am.
我不会为此道歉
And I won't apologize for that.
我已经让摩斯国务卿开始
I have asked Secretary Moss to begin
与俄罗斯进行双边会谈了
bilateral negotiations with Russia
希望你能尽快加入我们
in the hopes that you will join us soon.
夫人
Madame...
我真心希望你能加入我们
I do hope you join us.
因为我相信无论法方去哪  北约都会追随
Because I believe wherever France goes, NATO will follow.
我希望我们能在下次峰会更详细地讨论这个问题
I hope we can discuss this more fully at the next summit.
我也希望如此
I would like nothing more.
白宫安全网络许可
标记文件被删除
里特
Ritter.
我们找到那个混蛋了
We got the son of a bitch.
他在哪
Where is he?
西翼
The West Wing.
好了  目标在移动  直走右转
Okay, our guy's on the move. Go straight and take a right.
没错  继续走
Yeah. Keep going.
还有多远
How much farther?
走廊尽头左转
Take a left at the end of the hallway.
等等  等等  右转
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Actually take a right.
不  等等
No. Wait.
我到底要去哪  恰克
Where am I going, Chuck?
不  不  不  别啊  别
No, no, no, no. Come on. Come on.
怎么了
What happened?
我们要找的人
Our guy.
克隆了自己的电子足迹
He cloned his digital fingerprint.
临界状态
系统崩溃
可怜的孩子
Poor guy.
这可不是他预期的旅行
Not quite the trip he expected.
谁都没想到这趟会是这样
Not quite the trip anyone expected.
的确
True enough.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢什么
What for?
支持我
For standing by me.
这个嘛
Well...
你也没给我多少选择
you didn't give me much choice.
你要是栽了  我得和你一起栽
If you go down, I go down with you.
我是认真的
I'm being serious.
我也是
Well, I am, too.
你都要把我逼疯了  汤姆
You know, you drive me nuts, Tom.
你有时候真是太...学术了
You're just so damn... academic at times,
我都想给你的头来一巴掌
I want to slap you upside the head.
但我要是没看出你身上的特质  我就太糟了
But damn if I don't see something special in you,
某种特质
something that might --
甚至可能让你接近伟人
well, might even approach greatness...
只要你不马失前蹄
...if you don't trip over your own feet.
谢谢  我想该这么说
Thank you. I think.
但我们还留得青山在  不怕没柴烧
But we're not out of the woods yet. Not by a long shot.
你可能暂时挽回了
You may have salvaged some credibility
北约的一些信任
with NATO for the time being,
但稍后降落时会有
but we're gonna have a whole new firestorm
全新的暴风烈火等着我们
waiting for us when we land.
我知道
I know.
准备好了吗
You ready for it?
必须不准备好
I'm gonna have to be.
柯克曼总统将于今日下午返回
President Kirkman returns this afternoon
而政局却与他昨天离开时
to a very different political landscape
大相径庭
than the one he left just yesterday.
柯克曼面临艾尔萨卡事件难题
埃布·莱纳德的爆炸性声明
Abe Leonard's bombshell story,
指出艾尔萨卡不是
which asserts Al-Sakar was not responsible
袭击国会大厦的罪魁祸首
for the attack at the Capitol,
一举震动了华盛顿
sent shock waves through Washington,
对总统来说这时机不能更差了
and it couldn't have come at a worse time for the president,
他正好在第一次国际访问途中
who's at the height of his first international trip.
很多人称之为柯克曼不长的总统生涯中
Many are calling this the worst day
最糟的一天
of Kirkman's young presidency.
快走  快
Let's go! Let's go!
-快点  -向我六点钟方向前进
- Let's go! - Move up on my six.
-走  -跟上  走
- Let's go. - Follow 'em up. Go, go, go.
走
Go. Go, go.
在这
Here we go.
-不许动  -联调局  举起手来
- Freeze! - FBI! See those hands!
走
Go!
-没有人  -没有人
- Nothing. - Nothing, nothing.
警惕
Eyes open.
联调局  举起手来
FBI! Put your hands up!
-不许动  快点  -举起手来
- Don't move! Do it now! Now! - Hands up!
趴下  趴下
Get down! Down!
-走  -带他下楼
- Let's go. - Take him downstairs.
安全了  长官
We're all clear, sir.
打开所有的集装箱进行搜索
I want every container opened and searched.
威尔士在船上的某处  找到她
Wells is somewhere on board. Find her.
-是  长官  -走
- Yes, sir. - Let's go!
把他们带下来
Let's get them down there now.
趴在地上
On the ground!
这个没人
This one's clear!
没人
All clear!
全都没人  长官
All clear, sir.
-检查别的  -这个呢
- Let's check the others. - What about this one?
这个被焊封起来了  长官
It's welded shut, sir.
那就炸开
Well, blow it.
设置好了
Yeah, we're set here.
好了
Here we go.
准备好了
We're all set here.
启动炸药  要爆炸了  找掩护
Let's go! Fire in the hole! Cover!
-走  -门开了
- Go. - Door's open.
约翰·埃德加·胡佛联调局大楼
车库二层
趴在地上
On the ground right now!
手放在脑后
Get your hands behind your head!
-跪下  -跪下  快
- Get on your knees! -Get down! Now!